so a big movies guy I love movies movies
are really my thing except the horror
genre I can't do horror anymore they're
just too unrealistic I can't get on
board the last one that really just did
me in was the newest Czech Texas
Chainsaw Massacre movie I don't know if
you saw that it was edited unbidden Joel
calm down don't tense up too hard okay I
did it right but there was a scene like
I get it he's got a fake face he's run
around some people that's scary but
there was a scene in that movie where he
ran around terrorizing the Texas State
Fair I call BS on that everyone in Texas
has a gun there is there's no way he's
making it out they'd be like is that a
guy with a fake face finally roll
credits end of franchise
he could run around for days in the
Oregon State Fair sure sure that's fine
but not the Texas State Fair that's my
point they probably wouldn't even run
away in Oregon they'd just stand there
screaming doctor's opinion